Ted Robinson has been worried all the week.
Last Tuesday he received a letter from the local police.
In the letter he was asked to call at the station.
Ted wondered why he was wanted by the police, but he went to the station yesterday and now he is not worried any more.
At the station, he was told by a smiling policeman that his bicycle had been found.
Five days ago, the policeman told him, the b icycle was picked up in a small village four hundred miles away.
It is now being sent to his home by train.
Ted was most surprised when he heard the news.
He was amused too, because he never expected the bicycle to be found.
It was stolen twenty years ago when Ted was a boy of fifteen!